i want to thank you all for coming out
uh and supporting this event
uh this is this is amazing right here
what's happening here today represents
change and i want to just take
i want to just take a few moments please
you know i'm a pastor
and uh i need to bring
some perspective to what's going on here
the first thing i want to start with is
this i i
on behalf of my people
i apologize and when i say my people
i mean the christian churches in america
because you see god called
the churches to represent
how the cross of calvary
brings people together and yet
almost 50 years more than 50 years after
martin luther king
said that our church services are the
most
segregated hour in the united states of
america
we are still doing the same today
churches are modeling segregation
today cannot get it right how can the
church have anything to say
to the world how can the church have
anything to say to the community
we're supposed to be the ones with a
message
of unification
we have failed on behalf of the churches
i apologize
the second thing i want to share is this
you see the bible says that god made
man in his image and in his likeness
that doesn't mean one man he made
mankind
so when i read the bible i see that god
made the human
races
the race y'all didn't catch that
the race just one one way this one
one just one two just one
just
the bible says that god made man to
reflect his image
some of y'all don't know what god looks
like if you want
to go to the book of ezekiel the prophet
ezekiel had a vision of god and the
glory of god that he saw
was like a
[Applause]
the glory of rainbow is like a reindeer
where all the colors together
reflect the beauty and glory of god and
if god made man in his image
then the reason why we are all different
colors here today
is to reflect the glory of god
[Applause]
stay with me one race
[Music]
and i believe listen carefully i believe
that the devil hates the human race
which makes him the ultimate racist
and all he wants to do is to destroy the
glory of god
by turning the colors against one
another
so
[Applause]
i need to tell you this beloved because
you may not understand this but
plantations
still exist today
slavery still exists today
how how listen there's a plantation
called hate
and it's crop is racism
and the slave master the original racist
has employed slaves to work on his field
listen those who are racist
are simply doing the bidding of their
master
[Music]
those who are racist are simply slaves
on the racist plantation
yes slavery still exists today there are
people who are slaves
to ignorance slaves to hate
slaves to misunderstanding slaves to
racism
those are the real slaves
i know i know that that we have this
thing about being angry
being angry at them like it's them
versus us but remember beloved
if we are all to reflect the glory of
god and for one race then how stupid is
it
to be racist against your own race
[Applause]
one race many colors
how foolish is it to be racist against
your own
race
[Music]
so watch this in the old days the slave
master
used to because there were so many
slaves on the plantation
they have to make sure that the slaves
never trusted each other
because if they actually united and
recognize the real enemy
the slave master would be in trouble
there would be an uprising a rebellion
a slave rebellion
see so so listen guys
the whole objective is to keep the races
at war with one another not realizing
that if we were to unite preach that
word
and see who the real slave master is
we could have an uprising listen listen
listen
how many of you know who harriet tubman
is
you remember that the underground
railroad yeah and you know what they
would do
they would go back into enemy territory
to save their brothers and sisters from
[Applause]
you're probably not slavery like this
but guess what
the racist is your brother and sister
yes they are enslaved to racism but they
are our brothers they are our family
they are part of the rainbow and so
watch this they are simply
being slaves to ignorance and if we
truly love
we need to save them off the plantation
so so check this out what we need today
what we need today is some new
abolitionists
we need some new abolitionists who will
fight against slavery
who will go into enemy territory and
speak
sign me up
[Applause]
i please tell you what you're doing
you're being a slave to a greater power
we you need to be freed
that's how we solve this listen martin
luther king
realized that laws of the government
can only refrain or restrain
un restrained hearts that are not
restrained
he realized that laws could only go so
far if you want racism to end
that's a heart issue
[Music]
racists will find a way around any law
to be racist still so
listen we gotta go into enemy territory
as
abolitionists
this is not a popular message a popular
message is let's
let's burn stuff down let's do this
let's do that but beloved listen to me
in this time more than ever we need
abolitionists can i see if anyone out
there wants to be an abolitionist help
me out
yeah we need a new underground railroad
stop talking to your friends
you all have friends who may be racist
don't let them get away with it
if you truly love the human
[Music]
deliver your brethren from the
plantation
so that they can be free
one one race many colors
many colors one race one race
three colors